I speak the name of Jesus over you.
In your hurting, in your sorrow,
I will ask my God to move.
I speak the name because it's all that I
can do.
In desperation, I'll seek heaven and pray
this for you.
I pray for your healing.
The circumstances would change.
I pray that the fear inside would flee.
In Jesus' name.
I pray that a breakthrough would happen
today.
I pray miracles over your life.
In Jesus' name.
I speak the name of all authority.
Declaring blessings, every promise.
He is faithful to keep.
I speak the name no grave could ever hold.
He is greater.
He is stronger.
He's the God of possible.
I pray for your healing.
Circumstances would change
I pray that the fear inside would flee in Jesus' name
I pray that a breakthrough would happen today.
I pray miracles over your life, in Jesus' name.
In Jesus' name.
Oh, come believe it, come receive it.
Oh, the power of the Spirit is now forever
yours.
Come believe it, come receive it.
In the mighty name of Jesus, all things
are possible.
I pray for your healing, that
circumstances would change.
I pray that the fear inside would flee,
in Jesus' name.
I pray that a breakthrough would happen
today.
I pray miracles over your life,
in Jesus' name.
I pray for revival, a restoration of
faith.
I pray that the day would come alive,
in Jesus' name.
In Jesus' name.
......
Amen.
Hello brothers and sisters.
What a beautiful hymn.
Beautiful, beautiful hymn.
Happy Friday everyone.
First and foremost, let me see,
can everyone hear me?
I hope my voice is audible, okay?
Amen.
What a great pleasure to be here with all
of you.
And my name is Sister Telma.
And I live in Canada, Toronto,
to be exactly, brothers and sisters.
But enough about me a little bit.
I just wanted to say, why are we here,
right?
Each and every single one of you are here
because you love God.
You're a believer.
And one of our greatest hopes in our
hearts is to enter into the kingdom, right?
We all want to enter the kingdom of
heaven, brothers and sisters.
And why is that our greatest hope?
Because when we enter the kingdom,
we can welcome the Lord.
Our dreams can come true, right?
No longer will there be sorrow,
nor crying.
No longer sickness.
That's the beauty of it.
So, if we believe in
the Lord, but we fail to
welcome Him, it's going
to be an eternal regret.
Because look around, brothers and sisters.
What are the signs that
we should be looking
for when the Lord
returns in the last days?
The signs are happening, aren't they?
Especially because 2,000
years ago, the Lord Jesus
prophesied, And you shall
hear of wars and rumors of wars.
And see that you now be troubled.
For all these things must come to pass.
But the end is not yet.
For nation shall rise against nation,
and kingdom against kingdom.
For there shall be famine and pestilences
and earthquakes in diverse places.
So, I want to ask you all, brothers and
sisters, okay?
Take a look at this question.
Right?
Brothers and sisters, what do you think?
Are these prophecies being fulfilled right
now?
Do you feel like we're living in the last
days?
You can either answer with a yes or a no.
What do you think?
Do you feel like we're living in the last
days?
days as you look around the world,
see what's happening, the
wickedness, when you get on
the news and you just
hear sad things all the time?
What do you think?
Robert says, yeah.
Anyone else?
Robert says, yes, we're living in the last
days.
Teresa says, yes.
Anyone else care to answer?
Yeah, how does this make you feel?
Do you feel like we're living in the last
days?
Because I do, too.
I agree with Teresa.
I agree with Felicidad.
I agree with Sister Regina.
Regina also says yes.
Anyone else also have that feeling that we
are living in the last days?
Ah.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Laita says, yes, we are.
According to the current situation,
she's prophecies are being fulfilled.
Absolutely.
Laita.
The end times are happening right now.
Abraham says, yes, we are.
Colby says, yes.
Alex also says, yes.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Just look at the world, man.
Look what's happening, right?
The Russia and Ukraine war that has kicked
off back in 2022, that's still dragging on.
What about the Middle East?
You know the Middle East is always on
edge.
And the standoff between the U.S. and the Iran, it continues.
You see, marked by frequent
clashes and constant exchanges
of threats and things could
just blow up at any second.
Man, what about the plagues?
What about the plagues?
We've all lived through it.
For example, COVID.
The COVID pandemic hit almost every corner
of the globe.
And it's still lingering.
Did anyone hear about the new virus that's
coming out?
What's it called, the hantavirus?
Anyone else heard about the new
hantavirus?
That's just like, apparently it's here in
Toronto already.
Has it hit where you are already,
brothers and sisters?
There are some cases here in Canada.
Where I am, in my city, I think there are
seven cases here already.
I have a feeling with the World Cup,
it's going to be even worse.
It's going to be even worse.
Crazy, isn't it?
Disasters are happening left, right,
and center.
Ebola too, Laita says.
That's right, sister.
Look at the Turkey-Syria earthquake also
in 2023.
It leveled cities in seconds.
You see, some parts of the world are
dealing with extreme heat and drought.
While others are getting slammed with
non-stop floods.
And on top of everything, we're facing a
food crisis.
Brothers and sisters, the
UN keeps warning that
we're facing a food
shortage like never before.
You see, some places are already running
out of food.
I mean, famine is in some story of the
past.
It's happening right now.
That's why food is getting more expensive
because we're in a food crisis.
You see, all this tells us that we're
definitely in the last days.
And a lot of Christians are more eager now
more than ever.
Right?
We're eager for the Lord's return.
Because we know that
welcoming the Lord is one of
our only hope to be
protected through the disasters.
Now, my dear brothers and sisters,
right?
Have you really thought about how the Lord
will actually come in the last days?
Have you?
Have you thought about the Lord?
How he's going to come back in the last
days?
How we are supposed to welcome him?
Is this something that you think about on
a day-to-day basis?
Or this is something
that you haven't really
quite put a thought into
it, brothers and sisters?
Have you thought about how he's going to
come?
Well, if you have not thought about it,
then don't worry.
This will be our topic tonight,
okay?
Tonight we are here because we are going
to learn how does the Lord come?
How does he come?
Because you may, you know, some people may
say, Hey, that's not for us to worry about.
The Lord will come when he wants to and
however he wants to.
But you got to think about this,
brothers and sisters.
The Bible talks about the wise virgins and
the foolish virgins.
And when it comes to welcoming the Lord's
return, what makes a virgin wise?
And what does preparing oil really mean?
Because the Lord gave us this parable
2,000 years ago, right?
He said, He that seeks finds, to him that
knocks, it shall be opened.
You see, brothers and sisters,
there were 10 virgins.
Five were wise and five were foolish.
Does anyone know about the parable of the
10 virgins?
I think we know about the parable of the
10 virgins, right?
Let me send you a picture, brothers and
sisters.
You see, the wise virgins, they don't just
sit around and wait.
They don't wait.
The wise virgins, they prepare.
They prepare themselves with the truth and
with the knowledge regarding the Lord.
The Lord's second coming.
So they are able to receive the Lord when
He does come back.
That's the beauty of the wise virgins.
Whereas the foolish ones, they're
basically lukewarm about the whole thing.
They're lukewarm in their belief in God.
They just stubbornly stick to their own
notions and imaginations.
They don't seek.
They are not looking for the Lord's
return, brothers and sisters.
They don't care.
They don't care at all.
They don't look into the Lord's
intentions.
You see?
So even though they're
waiting, quotation mark,
they're going to miss their
chance to welcome Him.
You see, brothers and sisters, this
is not just another Bible study, okay?
We're talking about the important matter
of the Lord's coming.
Because it's soon.
This is about whether we can actually
welcome the Lord.
And gain a good destination in the end.
So if we want to survive the great
disasters.
If you want to be a wise virgin who gets
their oil ready.
And if you want to welcome the Lord's
return and have a good destination.
Then we're going to talk about...
What we're going to
talk about tonight is
critical for each and
every single one of us.
Alright, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
So, a little bit about myself,
brothers and sisters.
This is exactly what we're going to
discuss tonight.
A little bit about myself, as I already
said.
I live in Canada.
I live in Toronto, to be exact.
I come from a very big family.
I do have nine siblings.
I don't know if anyone else here has a big
family like I do.
Nine siblings.
It's quite big.
But, you know, having nine siblings really
taught me about unity, patience, love.
And the beauty of walking together in
truth.
And these lessons still shape how I see
fellowship today.
Because for me, brothers and sisters,
church, it's not just a meeting.
For me, church is family.
Just like all of you guys here tonight.
For me, us coming together like this to
learn about the Lord's return.
For me, we are all family.
And I see many of us have joined here
tonight.
So I want to say hello to each and every
single one of you.
I see we have Hamilton, Jeff and Abraham,
Delora, Linda.
We've got Vi, Robert, Alex.
Hello, Lisa and Samuel.
Oh, Brother Alex, you have 11?
Okay, you beat me.
Brother Robert has five siblings.
Okay, you guys beat me.
That's amazing.
Yeah, big family, eh?
Sorry.
Here we also have Brother Samuel.
We've got Jareen and Johnny and Marcy.
We've got Colby, Regina, Sisley.
We also have Therese.
We've got Cecile.
We've got Marie and Sister Annette is
here.
Michelle, Hodge, Elaine, Christiana and
Quinn.
And I'm pretty sure we have more brothers
and sisters who are joining us as well.
What a pleasure.
What a pleasure to be here with all of
you.
And like I said, I see all of you as my
family in Christ.
As long as we are together in spirit and
in truth.
We are family in Christ, brothers and
sisters.
So yes, welcome to the family.
Okay.
So my beloved brothers and
sisters, as you can see here,
we are going to learn so
much in the next four days.
Yes, we're going to be meeting together
for four days.
Okay.
So today marks the first one.
And we've got four more
days to go where we're
going to learn how exactly
does the Lord come back.
Then tomorrow we're going to learn what
work does he come to.
What does he come back to do?
Because obviously the work the Lord comes
back to do, it pertains to you and me.
And then on Sunday, we're going to talk
about God's management plan.
Okay.
We're going to talk about how did it all
start?
How did God start saving mankind?
And then on Monday, we have a very great
topic to share with all of you.
We're going to learn what does it mean to
hear God's voice.
Okay.
I think this is such a great topic for us
to hear.
And also to brothers
and sisters, as you can
see, there are so many
of us here in the group.
I just want to give you guys a kind
reminder that it is very important that
when we do join the fellowship,
you can mute your mics.
Okay.
And if you're on camera, you necessarily
do not have to be on camera.
This is an audio Bible study and audio
fellowship.
So if you don't feel like comfortable being
on camera, you can turn off your camera.
But make sure that your microphone is
muted.
Okay.
If you don't know how to
mute your mics, brothers and
sisters, take a look at
the bottom of your screen.
At the bottom of your screen, hello,
Haj.
Hello, brother.
At the bottom of your screen, you're going
to see like a microphone button.
You're also going to see a camera button.
You're going to see a person with a plus
button on it.
You're going to see the volume with like
extra sounds on it.
Make sure to hit the one with the
microphone.
Okay, if you hit on that, it'll mute you.
If you hit on that again, it'll unmute
you.
Okay, so if you're interested in reading
as well throughout the fellowship,
because I will be sending Bible verses,
I'll be sending scriptures.
If you're interested in
reading, by all means,
please open up your mic
and you can read for us.
Of course, if you're interested in
reading, no pressure at all.
No pressure at all.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
All right.
Thanks be to God.
I pray that God leads and guides our
fellowship here for tonight.
But before that happens, let's all begin
with an opening prayer.
Okay, let's all quiet our hearts,
brothers and sisters.
And let us begin with an opening prayer.
Let's bow our head, put our hands
together.
And let's pray.
Amen.
Dear Heavenly Father, Almighty God,
we thank you for this special time of
fellowship that you have brought all of us
here together, dear God.
I believe this is all of our first time
being here.
Meeting one another, dear God.
But we come, we come in spirit.
And we want to come in truth, dear Lord.
We pray for the unity that you have
brought us and the wonderful environment
that you set out for us just to have
fellowship with you.
And having fellowship with many brothers
and sisters from all over the world.
Dear God, this is such a
special time because we see
so many disasters are
happening already, dear God.
And the only way that
we can escape these
disasters is actually
by coming towards you.
By seeking.
Your truth, dear Lord.
Because after all, only the truth can set
us free.
And only you have the truth, dear Lord.
We pray that this fellowship tonight will
give us an insight on how exactly will you
come back in the last days and what we
ourselves need to prepare for in order to
be a wise virgin, dear God, in order to
prepare enough oil and to have enough
faith regarding your second coming.
Dear Lord, we're so thankful.
We're very thankful that
we get to participate in this
online fellowship right
at the comfort of our own.
Dear God, I pray that we can all have a
quiet heart before you, dear Lord,
so that we can understand the practicality
of coming together to seek your word and
how beneficial it can be for our spiritual
life.
I'm so excited to meet all the brothers
and sisters here, dear Lord.
I know we're all going to grow together in
spirit and in truth.
And this is something that you approve of.
And we may not know each other.
We may be strangers, dear God.
But right now, we are connected in spirit.
So we thank you wholeheartedly for this
precious time that we get to be here,
seeking your prophecies
and understanding
your will, especially
in these days and time.
Dear God, I put all brothers and sisters
into your hands, myself included,
and we pray that the
Holy Spirit will enlighten
each and every single
one of our hearts.
We give you all the praise, all the honor
and all the glory.
In Jesus' name, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
All right.
Amen, everybody.
Thanks be to God.
All right.
All right, brothers and sisters.
So let's get started.
Okay.
Let's get started here for tonight.
So I want to ask you all a
question because tonight we're
going to talk about how
exactly does the Lord come back?
Okay.
So my question to all of you is this.
How exactly do you think the Lord is going
to come?
How did you grow up learning about the
Lord's second coming, brothers and sisters?
Yeah, what did you grow up learning about
the Lord's second coming?
How do you think the Lord is going to come
back?
Well, you know, there are so many people
in the religious world, right?
That they say that, hey, the Lord is going
to come on a white cloud.
Right?
And they say this because of revel...
exactly.
I see, Teresa.
I knew it.
Right?
Many people in the
religious world, they say
the Lord is going to
come on a white cloud.
And they say this because of Revelation
1.7.
Revelation 1.7 reads, Behold, he comes
with clouds, and every eye shall see him,
and they also which
pierced him, and all
kindreds of the earth
shall wail because of him.
So they figure when the Lord returns,
the trumpets will sound.
A roaring, lion sound will sound, and
he'll descend on a cloud in all his glory.
Right?
That's what the entire religious world
thinks, right, brothers and sisters?
And honestly, the Lord
descending on a white
cloud, that's definitely
going to happen.
No one is doubting that at all.
That's going to happen.
There's no doubt about that.
But have you ever stopped to think?
Is that the only way?
Is that the only way that you think he's
coming?
Think about it.
What actually happens when the Lord Jesus
descends on a white cloud?
Read that prophecy very careful.
Right?
Look.
In Revelation 1.7, it says, All kindreds
of the earth shall wail because of him.
You see, logically speaking, shouldn't the
Lord coming on a white cloud, you know,
be a huge day of celebration for
everybody?
Shouldn't the Lord coming
on a white cloud, you
know, be a huge day of
celebration for everybody?
But ask yourself, why does the prophecy
say, All kindreds of the earth shall wail?
Do you know there's a mystery to uncover
here?
There's a mystery to uncover here,
brothers and sisters.
Because the truth is, the Lord descending
on a white cloud will happen for sure.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
It's not.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
But it's not the only way he's coming.
There are so many
prophecies in the Bible that
talks about the Lord
descending on a white cloud.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
We're going to pay attention to all of
them.
Amen, Sister Quinn.
Absolutely.
You see, because if we just read one or
two verses, and then say that the Lord is
definitely going to come on a white cloud,
then aren't we just jumping to conclusion?
We could easily miss.
We could easily miss
our chance to welcome
the Lord and end up
being eliminated by him.
So first, brothers and sisters, I want
all of us here to take a deep breath.
Can we all take a deep breath right now,
brothers and sisters?
Oh, sorry, Mr. Quinn.
Sorry, my dear brother.
Let's all take a deep breath right now.
All right.
Everybody took a deep breath.
We all took a deep breath.
All right.
Everybody take a deep breath.
And let's really dive
into the other prophecies
about the Lord's return
in the last days, okay?
Because when we do that, we'll find a lot
of new enlightenment.
You see, the Bible has a lot of prophecies
about the Lord's return.
Some from Jesus himself, some are from
men, and some are from God.
Some are from angels, okay?
Now, if we want to know how the Lord is
really going to come, well, whose
prophecies do you think is the most
accurate?
Which prophecy do you think is the most
accurate, brothers and sisters?
Would you say the Lord's prophecies,
men's prophecies, or angels' prophecies?
Which one is the most accurate?
I think we can all agree.
That is the Lord's prophecies,
right?
Exactly, Brother Gregory.
Most definitely the Lord.
Amen, Sister Yanni.
Amen, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Sister Annette.
There's no doubt about that.
So, many of us are saying the Lord's
prophecy.
Amen, Sister Annette.
But look at the religious world today.
Amen, Colby.
Most people only quote prophecies for men.
They're all waiting for the Lord to appear
publicly on a white cloud.
But they're actually ignoring what Jesus
himself said.
So for us, in order to
welcome the Lord's return,
we need to go according
to the Lord's own words.
Because that's our only real shot at
welcoming Him.
So tonight, we're going to look at what
the Lord Jesus' prophecies personally say.
And I'm going to send some prophecies from
the bible.
But before I do, I want to make two things
clear.
Two things super clear, okay?
Two things super clear here tonight.
The prophecies that I'm about
to share are regarding the second
coming of the Lord Jesus in
the last days, the second coming.
And two, these are not prophecies from
angels or from men.
These are the Lord's own words.
All right, brothers and sisters?
Two things, okay?
We need to understand.
We are now talking about the second coming
of Christ.
All right?
And also the prophecies that we are going
to read are prophecies from the Lord Jesus.
Everybody ready?
Are we all ready, brothers and sisters?
You can put praying hands.
You can put praying hands into the group
chest so I know that you are ready.
Okay, we're ready.
I love that.
Thanks, sweet.
God, everybody's coming ready.
Okay, that's awesome.
So let me send the prophecies here.
Let's take a look at the prophecies,
okay?
And would any brother
or sister like to volunteer
to read these
prophecies for us tonight?
Does anyone want to open up their mic?
Would anyone like to open up their mics
and read for us tonight?
Let's see.
Anybody want to read?
Regina, would you like to read?
Or Brother Quinn, would you like to read?
If not, don't you worry, brothers and
sisters, okay?
If not, I can also read as well,
okay?
That's no problem at all.
All right?
We're ready?
Okay, perfect.
Let's listen.
For as the lightning comes
out of the east and shines even
to the west, so shall also the
coming of the Son of Man be.
Matthew 24, 27.
For as the lightning that lightens out of
one part under heaven shines to the other
part under heaven, so shall also the Son
of Man be in his day.
But first must he suffer many things and
be rejected of this generation.
Luke 17, 24-25.
Therefore be you also
ready, for in such an
hour as you think not
the Son of Man comes.
Matthew 24, 44.
As the days of Noah weren't are, so
shall also the coming of the Son of Man be.
Matthew 24, 37.
And at midnight there was a cry made,
"'Behold, the Bridegroom comes.
Go you out to meet Him." Matthew 25,
6.
If therefore you
shall not watch.
" Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So, brothers and sisters, I have a
question for all of you.
After listening to these prophecies over
here, right?
In all these prophecies from
the Lord Jesus himself, does
he ever mention coming down
on a cloud for everyone to see?
What do you think?
Amen, Sister Annette.
Anyone else?
In any of the prophecies,
did you see him saying
that he comes on a white
cloud for everyone to see?
Amen, Sister Regina.
Ah, good eye.
Amen, Brother Gregory.
Amen, Felicidad.
Good eye.
Good eye, brothers and sisters.
No, not once, right?
Amen, Colby.
You see, the Lord's
return is not limited to
that one way that we
have always imagined.
In fact, these prophecies keep
highlighting four key points.
What are the four key points, brothers and
sisters?
Take a look.
It talks about the Son of Man.
It talks about him coming like a thief.
It also talks about we have to listen for
God's voice, as well as he'll be rejected
by this generation.
So the big question is this.
What does it really mean that he comes as
the Son of Man?
What's the meaning that he is coming like
a thief?
And why is listening for God's voice the
only way to welcome the Lord?
And why would the Lord be rejected again
when he returns?
Don't you think that this is a huge
mystery for us to unpack?
Absolutely.
So let's dive in, brothers and sisters.
Let's get to know these key points,
right?
Let's get to know what each of these key
points truly mean.
You see, the first one was the Son of Man.
The Son of Man, right?
That's the first key point that we're
going to take a look at, okay?
Because all of the
prophecies mention the Son
of Man comes or the
coming of the Son of Man.
But have you ever stopped to ask yourself,
what exactly is the Son of Man?
And some people will say, well,
that's easy.
That's the Lord Jesus.
He's the Son of Man.
But there's a deeper meaning, brothers and
sisters, okay?
Yes, the Son of Man is the Lord Jesus.
But there is a deeper meaning.
Let me send you a question.
What is the Son of Man?
Now, before you answer the question,
I'm going to give you a clue.
Now, the clue is in the word itself.
Son of Man.
I gave you the answer.
Now, what do you think?
Is it A, God's spirit or a spiritual body,
very supernatural?
Or would you say B?
Born of flesh, who looks human and goes
through a normal process of growing up,
ordinary and normal?
Or C, I'm not too sure.
I did not get the clue.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
This one is pretty easy.
Son of Man.
What's your answer now?
You can answer.
Amen, Sister Regina.
Amen.
Amen, Brother Gregory.
Amen, Sister Felicidad.
Amen, Brother Colby.
Anyone else, brothers and sisters?
Did you catch it?
Amen, Yves.
Amen, Robert.
Oh, all brothers and sisters are catching
it.
Amen, Yenny.
Anyone else?
What do you think?
Cecile, Marie, Annette?
What do you think, Annette?
Did you catch it?
Edgar, Angela, Mark, Charlie, Elaine,
Christina, Brother Quinn.
What do you think, Brother Quinn?
What do you think?
What about Cecile, Daryl, Edgar,
and Annette?
Which one?
Amen, Annette.
Good catch.
Good catch, Annette.
Amen.
What about Clara, Delora, Jeff,
Abraham, Hamilton?
Amen, Abraham.
Makes me happy to be here too,
my dear brother.
Makes me happy.
Amen, Sister Theresa.
Amen, Charlie.
Amen.
Okay.
Brothers and sisters.
Great sharing, everybody.
Everyone actually got the answer,
correct.
The correct answer is, in fact,
B.
Everyone that I said your name out loud,
yeah, you got the correct answer.
B is the correct answer, brothers and
sisters.
Great sharing, everybody.
Yeah, you should be proud of yourself,
eh?
You know what the Son of Man refers to.
For those who didn't catch it,
brothers and sisters, the Son of Man,
it means God becoming flesh.
Yeah, it means God becoming flesh.
The Son of Man basically refers to a
person who was born of a human,
like Annette shared, right?
With normal humanity and a normal growth
process.
Because, brothers and sisters,
pay attention, right?
If it were a spirit, you could not call it
the Son of Man.
And I'll give you an example.
In the Old Testament, God is spirit.
You can't see him, you can't touch him.
So he is...
No worries, brother Quinn.
No worries.
You can listen, okay, my brother?
You see?
God is spirit.
In the Old Testament, God worked directly
as a spirit.
He was never called the Son of Man.
At all.
At all, brothers and sisters.
He was never called the Son of Man.
Some people even have seen angels.
Angels are spiritual beings.
You can't even call them Son of Man
either.
You see, the Son of Man specifically
refers to God becoming.
On the outside, he looks like a regular
person.
He's born of flesh, grows up normally,
and lives a normal life.
With normal needs.
What are the normal needs of life?
Eating, dressing, and sleeping.
And more, right?
And that's what the Son of Man is.
Think of the Lord Jesus.
The Lord Jesus, from the outside,
there was nothing special about him.
He was a normal, ordinary person living
among.
Man.
You see, the Lord
Jesus prophesied that he
would return as the Son
of Man in the last days.
That means he will become flesh a second
time in order to save us.
So when we say God becomes flesh,
it means God's very substance takes on a
physical body.
It means God becomes a man.
God becomes a man.
So basically, the God of heaven.
He takes on flesh and becomes a person.
He has a physical body and normal
humanity.
Like nothing supernatural about him at
all.
You can see him.
You can touch him.
He genuinely lives among people.
Living life right alongside us when he
becomes flesh.
So when the Lord Jesus talks about the
coming of the Son of Man, he was talking
about God returning in the last days by
becoming flesh a second time.
So the coming.
The coming of the Son of Man, it means God
becoming flesh a second time.
Now, I know some of you may be wondering,
well, if he really becomes flesh again,
why didn't the prophecies just say God
will become flesh?
Why didn't the prophecy say that?
Why would the prophecy say some Son of Man
will appear?
Well, brothers and sisters, well,
that's just how prophecies work, right?
Prophecies.
What is a prophecy?
Prophecies are a foretelling
of what's to happen,
meaning there are always
a bit of mysteries within.
So because think about it.
If everything were spelled out plainly for
us, then it wouldn't be a prophecy anymore.
It would be called a plain statement.
But for us who are
truly seeking, we always
like to dig deeper into
the term Son of Man.
And through that, you may get some
enlightenment.
And you'll come to the realization that
Son of Man, it means God becoming flesh.
All right?
Now, my beloved brothers and sisters,
I know this might be the first time you're
hearing this, but let's not jump to any
conclusion just yet.
I really hope you'll all keep listening
with a humble heart.
And as we go on, you'll see even more
proof that God truly returns.
By becoming flesh, a second time in the
last days, okay?
Listen until the very end, and it'll make
a lot of sense, okay?
That's the first key point, brothers and
sisters.
The Son of Man.
But if you continue to go deeper,
right?
It talks about the Lord being rejected by
this generation again.
Look what the Lord Jesus said.
For as the lightning, the light that is
out of one part under heaven, shines to
the other part under heaven, so shall also
the Son of Man be.
But first must he suffer many things and
be rejected of this generation.
Look right there, it
says, first must he suffer
many things and be
rejected of this generation.
Brothers and sisters, this is even more
proof that the Lord will become flesh again.
And remember, I want you to think about
it.
It's only because God becomes the Son of
Man again, appearing among us,
looking completely normal and ordinary,
that some people would dare to write him
off as a regular person and actually
condemn and resist him.
Also, the idea of God becoming flesh as
the Son of Man in the last days,
it actually goes against people's
expectations, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
It goes against people's expectations.
Because why?
Why?
Because people just can't wrap around.
They can't wrap around their heads that
God will become flesh a second time.
And that's exactly why it says people will
resist him and will condemn him again.
And that's why God suffers and is rejected
by our generation all over again.
Now, when we say rejected and suffers,
we're not talking about suffering on the
cross like he did 2,000 years ago.
Because remember, God
becoming flesh in the last days,
it's really to prepare his
people into the kingdom.
Now, there are going to be a lot of people
that will reject him again.
And this is a way that God
suffers because he's coming back
again to actually prepare
us for the final destination.
But people are going to reject him.
That's God suffering.
It's almost like, let's say you have a you
have a you have a children or you have
children and your children don't want to
listen to you.
They rebel against you.
They condemn you.
Don't you suffer?
Of course you do.
That's your child.
Well, we're God's children.
If we don't obey him, if we don't believe
in him and accept him, that's also a form
of God suffering as well, brothers and
sisters.
Okay.
So yes, he suffers again because of
people's rejection.
Just like how they rejected him 2,000
years ago.
You see, I mean like if God didn't become
flesh, if he just showed up in the sky as
a spirit, if he just showed up riding on a
white cloud for the whole world to see
him, then you have to think who would
reject him?
Who would resist him if he just came up in
the sky?
Nobody would.
And if that were the
case, then the prophecy
first, must he suffer many
things and be rejected?
That could never come true.
So really, brothers and
sisters, when the Lord
returns, he will definitely
become flesh again.
And there's zero doubt about it.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
That's the first key point.
The son of man, refers to God becoming
flesh.
Is everyone clear on this key point so
far?
Are we clear so far, brothers and sisters?
That's the first key point that we read
from the Lord's words.
Give me praying hands to
make sure that you are clear
so that I can move on to
the next key point, okay?
There's so many.
Remember, there was four.
That's only the first one.
All right.
So, all right.
Amen, everybody.
Thanks, God.
So then let's move on to the second key
point.
Right?
Which was, I come as a thief.
The Lord also said, if therefore you shall
not watch, I come as a thief.
Behold, I come as a thief.
Now, a lot of people
ask, what does it mean for
the Lord when he says
he's coming back as a thief?
How is this prophecy fulfilled?
Well, brothers and sisters, coming like a
thief is an obvious metaphor.
Okay?
It's a metaphor for how the Lord is going
to come back.
It's a metaphor.
Okay?
Yes, you can type your question,
Annie.
You can type your question.
It's an obvious metaphor for how he comes
back.
You see?
When you think of a thief, you think of
someone who is sneaking in quietly.
Exactly.
You don't know when he's going to come
back.
Right?
Exactly, Thomas.
You don't know when he's going to come
back.
That's what a thief does.
A thief is sneaky without no one noticing.
Now, it isn't some big, public,
spectacular way that he comes,
brothers and sisters, how the whole world
is going to know about it.
No.
It means that when the
Lord comes back in the
last days, he will arrive
in secret like a thief.
Now, coming like a thief, it means two
things.
One, it means nobody knows the day or hour
of the Lord's return.
Nobody.
And two, the Lord's identity will be
hidden when he comes.
And he won't be easy to spot or to
recognize.
And that is why the prophecy in Revelation
mentions, I come as a thief.
Brothers and sisters, that also means that
when the Lord comes back in the last days,
he'll once again become flesh as the son
of man.
That's the metaphor, brothers and sisters.
He's becoming flesh again.
I come as a thief.
You're not going to recognize me by
outward appearance.
That's literally him coming back in the
flesh.
Nobody knows the exact time he's coming.
And on top of that, his identity will not
be obvious.
Even if people see him, they won't
recognize that he is God.
They won't know that he is God.
So to come like a thief, it means he's
coming in the flesh.
It also means he's coming unexpected and
unexpected.
Unrecognized.
And I want you to think about 2,000 years
ago, okay?
I don't know how many of you are very
familiar with the Bible, but it's okay.
We're here to learn, right?
Now think about this, brothers and
sisters.
2,000 years ago, when the Lord Jesus was
working in the flesh, did people recognize
him just by looking at his outward
appearance?
What do you think?
Did people recognize him just by his
outward appearance 2,000 years ago?
Yes or no?
Like, for example, when they see Jesus,
did they say, oh my God?
Oh, that's the Messiah.
Let's follow him.
Was that the case, everybody?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
No.
Right?
That was not the case at all.
Nobody recognized him as the Messiah.
Amen, everybody.
Great sharing.
The answer is no.
So to come like a thief, it means his
arrival is unexpected.
It means his identity is unrecognizable.
It means the secret arrival in the flesh.
You see?
On the outside, the Lord Jesus was just an
ordinary son of man.
It was really hard for people to recognize
that he was God.
I mean, if people could tell that he was
the Messiah just from his appearance,
then think about it.
Why would they nail him to the cross?
So it shows that we can't recognize God
just by the outward appearance of his flesh.
And there are plenty of examples in the
Bible, too, brothers and sisters.
For example, the Samaritan woman at the
well.
I think we all know about the story of the
Samaritan woman.
You see, Jesus asked her.
Right?
Jesus asked her for a drink.
And she thought he was a regular stranger.
Right?
She thought that he was a stranger.
She called him a Jew.
She said, you're a Jew.
I'm a Samaritan.
I can't give you a glass of water.
That's because outwardly, the son of man
looked normal.
Brothers and sisters.
It seems like some brothers and sisters
have their microphones open.
Please mute your mics, okay?
Brothers and sisters, please mute your
mics.
Smiley, please mute your mic, okay?
Please mute your mics, Smiley,
thank you.
Thank you.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
So outwardly, the son of man looks just
like an ordinary person.
And that's exactly why people cannot
recognize him by sight.
Right?
It's just like how you can tell someone is
a thief by looking at them.
So the prophecy in
Revelation, I come as a thief, it
points directly to God
becoming flesh a second time.
It's a mystery, but it's not that much of
a mystery, brothers and sisters,
because we're going to find out how can we
know?
How will we be able to know?
Which brings me to the fourth key,
the third or fourth key point.
All right?
Oh, so brothers and sisters, before I
continue, now you understand.
To come like a thief, it's a metaphor that
God will become flesh again.
Everyone clear on this point before we talk
about how are we going to recognize him?
Everyone clear so far?
I come as a thief is literally just a
metaphor.
Okay?
Just means you're not going to recognize
him when he becomes flesh because you're
not going to recognize him by his outward
appearance.
That's all it means.
Okay?
Now this is where it gets good.
All right?
This is where it gets good.
Take a look.
At this point, we're all thinking now,
man, if the Lord comes back as the son of
man in the last days, but then some people
say, well, if the Lord returns normal,
an ordinary son of man, and we can't tell
that he is God just by looking at him,
how are we going to recognize him?
Oh, brothers and sisters, how are we going
to recognize him?
Does anyone know?
How are we going to recognize him,
brothers and sisters?
If we can't recognize him by
his outward appearance, what
is the best way to recognize
Christ when he becomes flesh?
What do you think?
All I need is just one answer.
Amen, Neves.
Neves got it.
Amen, Annette, too.
Annette and Neve, you guys hit right.
You guys hit the point.
That's right.
Brothers and sisters, the Lord said,
my sheep hear my voice.
I know them.
They follow me.
Behold, I stand at the door and knock.
If any man hear my voice
and opens the door, I will
come into him, will step
with him, and he with me.
Yeah, that's right, brothers and sisters,
right?
So just looking at the prophecies,
How?
How do we welcome the Lord, right?
Just looking at the prophecy, how do we
welcome the Lord?
Do we use our ears to listen or our eyes
to listen?
Or our eyes to see?
What are you going to use, brothers and
sisters?
What are you going to use?
Your ears to listen or your eyes to see?
What are you going to use, brothers and
sisters?
Because I know what I'm going to use.
Amen.
Amen, everybody.
I see everyone's emoji.
Yeah, you're going to use your ears,
right?
That's right.
Right.
You're going to use your ears to listen.
And that is why we can only recognize the
Lord by listening.
Now this is even more
proof that the Lord's return in
the last days is by becoming
flesh as the Son of Man.
Because outwardly, he's just a regular
person.
Completely normal and ordinary.
Nothing supernatural at all.
If we just use our eyes, it's easy to
mistake the Lord for an ordinary man and
fail to recognize him, like many people
did 2,000 years ago.
It's only by listening to the Lord's
voice, listening to the word he speaks,
and the truth he expresses, that we can
recognize him when he returns.
Wow, brothers and sisters.
I mean, right?
Think about it.
If the Lord only...
If the Lord only came down on a white
cloud, everyone would see.
Everyone would recognize him immediately.
Right?
If he came on a white cloud, we wouldn't
need to listen to hear his voice.
We would just trust in our eyes.
And from all of this, we
can absolutely be certain
that the Lord's return will
happen in the flesh first.
And the only way to recognize the Son of
Man is by listening.
Listening to his voice.
You see, you can identify
him by... the words he speaks.
Right?
That's why the Lord said, My sheep hear my
voice.
I know them, and they follow me.
You see, brothers and sisters?
Why did he say, hear my voice?
There's a reason why he said it.
He didn't just say it so
you can, you know, recite
the Bible verse over
and over and over again.
You've got to understand the key.
The key point into it.
Hear my voice.
Why?
Because he returns.
He returns in secret.
So when God becomes flesh a
second time, there are going to
be two kinds of people when
it comes to welcoming the Lord.
That's where the parable of the wise
virgins and the foolish virgins come in.
So when God becomes flesh again, there are
two kinds of people, brothers and sisters.
One, there are the wise virgins.
Obviously, the wise virgins, those are
God's people.
Right?
Because the moment they
hear the words coming from
the Son of Man, they
will feel that it's the truth.
That it carries authority and power.
And right then, in their hearts, they are
certain that these words are God's voice.
And that's how the wise virgins hear God's
voice.
And that's how they welcome the
bridegroom.
What about another kind of people?
The foolish virgins.
They are not the sheep, they are the
goats.
They are the goats, brothers and sisters.
Right?
They can't recognize the Lord by listening
to His voice.
They only look at His outward appearance.
They judge the Son of Man to be just an
ordinary person.
They even go so far as to condemn and
reject Him.
And as a result, they will be abandoned by
the Lord.
And they will end up weeping and gnashing
their teeth in the great disasters.
Womp womp.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
Now you see, the Lord appears and works in
the flesh as the Son of Man in secret.
Right?
When He comes back.
The Lord Jesus prophesied, brothers and
sisters.
He prophesied this.
So you can't deny it.
You can't deny the word of your Creator.
Right?
But it does lead many
people to still say,
well, Sister Thelma,
what about Revelation?
Revelation 1, 7.
Well, what about it?
Right?
Well, let's bring it back up again.
They will say, Sister Thelma,
you just said that the Lord Jesus
will become flesh again as the
Son of Man to come on earth.
It has a solid biblical basis.
I get it.
And I totally agree.
But what about this verse here in the book
of Revelation?
Isn't this talking about the Lord coming
on a white cloud?
Isn't that a contradiction?
How do you explain this?
Okay, let's talk about
it, brothers and sisters,
because it might seem a
little contradiction at first.
But in reality, there's no contradiction
at all.
All right?
And I want to help you understand it
perfectly.
So first and foremost, every single
prophecy in the Bible, it must be fulfilled.
But they happen in stages, step by step.
So both the coming of the Son of Man and
descending upon a cloud will happen.
But there is an order to it, brothers and
sisters.
There's an order to it.
So you tell me, which one do you think
comes first?
Which one do you think comes first?
Do you think the appearance of the Son of
Man comes first?
Or descending on a white cloud comes
first?
What do you think will come first?
The Son of Man?
Or descending on a white cloud?
Feel free to type, okay?
Amen, Sister Regina.
You got it, sister.
Amen, Colby.
You got it.
Amen, Brother Gregory.
Anyone else?
Amen, Felicidad, Teresa.
You got it.
Brother Robert, so close.
So close, my dear brother.
So close.
But don't worry, we'll talk about it,
okay?
Anyone else, brothers and sisters?
Which one will come first?
The appearance of the Son of Man or coming
on a white cloud?
I think so far, everybody is actually on
the right spot.
Amen, Neves.
Amen, Emmy.
What about you, Annette?
Have you thought about it?
Which one comes first?
So far?
Good job, everybody.
It's literally, the Lord will
return by first becoming
flesh and arriving in secret
to appear and do his work.
And then he will descend on a white cloud.
That's right, Brother Edgar.
Brothers and sisters, the appearance of
the Son of Man, that comes first.
You see, from the prophecies, you could
see it's split into two stages.
There is the secret arrival and there is
the public arrival.
They will both happen, by the way.
No one is denying it.
They will both happen, my dear brothers
and sisters.
It's just the fact that you need to know
what comes first.
And that is the appearance.
Amen.
The appearance of the Son of Man first.
That comes first.
You see, first, the Lord, the Lord coming
like a thief, it means he's coming flesh
and arriving in secret to express the truth
and to carry out the work of judgment.
Yes, brothers and sisters, the primary
goal here is to make a group of overcomers.
It is to fulfill the prophecy that
judgment must begin at the house of God.
You see, this work begins the moment God
becomes flesh, arrives in secret,
and starts to express the truth to judge
all of mankind.
First, he does the work of judgment
beginning at the house of God.
God actually purifies and saves those who
can hear his voice, who can come before
him, and God will make them into
overcomers.
You see, the work of
making a group of people
into overcomers, that
hasn't happened yet.
It only happens when the Lord comes back
again.
And then that's when God returns to Zion
and the great disasters will begin.
Now, God will use the disasters to do
what?
To punish and destroy this old
world and destroy the wicked,
those who rejected him again,
those who condemned him again.
And that's when his work of judgment in
the last days will reach its peak.
And only after the great disasters will
God finally appear on earth.
But God appearing on a white cloud,
brothers and sisters, it's to reward the
good, the true believers, to finally go and
to rest with them and to punish the evil.
And at that point, God's work of judgment
will be completed.
And that's when God's kingdom will finally
appear.
That's when his kingdom will finally
appear, my dear brothers and sisters.
So the Lord's return, yes, it happens in
two stages.
No one is denying the Lord coming on a
white cloud.
It's going to happen.
It's just that there are steps to it.
You see, before the disasters,
he comes as the Son of
Man to express the truth and
to do the work of judgment.
That's the salvation period, brothers and
sisters.
And then after the disasters,
he descends on a white cloud
as a spiritual body to reward
the good and punish the evil.
So as you could see here, brothers and
sisters, both ways of the Lord's return,
before the disasters and after the
disasters, coming secretly by becoming
flesh as the Son of Man
and publicly descending
on a white cloud, are
biblical prophecies.
And both will be fulfilled, one after
another.
But you want to know what the difference
is?
Right?
What is the difference?
Because what happens?
What happens if you're only waiting for
the Lord to descend on a white cloud?
What happens if you reject him when he
comes secretly like a thief?
Have you ever thought about it?
Have you thought about it if you reject
the Lord who comes back as the Son of Man?
I think we all know what the consequences
are, right?
To figure this out, you
got to know what work the
Lord will do when he
arrives as the Son of Man.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
You got to know.
You see, the Lord becoming flesh,
and coming in secret before the disasters,
it really is to make a group of
overcomers.
That's right, Sister Felicidad.
If you don't accept him, you'll be
destroyed.
Because him coming in the flesh is because
his work is not done.
That's right, Brother Gregory.
You'll be lost.
You'll be wandering around, not knowing
where to go.
You see, God coming
back in the flesh again,
it's because we know
that he has got work to do.
He needs to make us into an overcomer.
He needs to make us into the first fruits
that God will complete.
And only we, the overcomers, will be
qualified to enter God's kingdom.
So really, the Lord becoming flesh again,
and coming on a white cloud, right?
It's different.
When he becomes flesh and coming in
secret, that's the salvation period.
That's the salvation stage.
It's the work of purifying and making
people perfect.
Because come on, brothers and sisters.
Are we perfect?
No, we're not.
The Son of Man still needs to make us
perfect.
We're not perfect yet, brothers and
sisters.
Right?
That needs to happen first.
Because by the time we see the Lord on a
white cloud, it's because he has already
perfected a group of people, those who can
hear God's voice.
So if we want to welcome the Lord only
when he comes on a white cloud,
then you have already missed the stage.
Of perfection.
You have already missed the stage when he
perfected a group of overcomers.
It'll be too late.
You'll be eliminated.
Just like brothers and sisters are
sharing.
And the loss you'll suffer will be huge.
Because by the time you see the Lord
coming on a white cloud, it's all over.
That's the exact moment when all nations
will wail.
Now this is the true
meaning of this fulfillment
right over here,
brothers and sisters.
Behold.
He comes with clouds, and every eye shall
see him, and they also which pierced him.
And all kindreds of the earth shall wail
because of him.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Many will wail because of him.
You see, wailing is not a good word.
I'll tell you that right now.
Wailing, brothers and sisters?
Let me tell you what the true meaning of
wailing is, okay?
Wailing is a prolonged cry of pain,
of grief.
And of anger.
Look at that.
You see?
When all eyes see him
coming on a white cloud,
it says all kindreds
of the earth shall wail.
Meaning you're going to be crying in so
much pain, in grief, and in anger.
Because why?
When someone told you that the Lord will
become flesh again, you rejected,
you denied.
Because you're too arrogant.
Too ignorant of the truth.
So the only way for you to do is wail.
Because you missed it.
You missed it, brothers and sisters.
And I pray that that's not us.
That's why we're here to seek the truth,
brothers and sisters.
Because we are not denying the Lord will
come on a white cloud.
That's going to happen.
You just need to know what happens first.
Which is the coming of the Son of Man.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So, let me ask you all a question,
okay?
At which stage is it best for us to
welcome the Lord?
Now this is a personal question,
okay, brothers and sisters?
Now that's up to you.
That's up to you.
At what stage is best for you to welcome
the Lord?
Would you say A.
You're just going to wait for him to come
on a white cloud in a spiritual body?
Or would you say B.
I'm going to wait for him when he becomes
flesh a second time.
And when he returns in secret.
Or C.
I don't know when I want to welcome him.
I never thought about it.
What do you think brothers and sisters?
What do you think Charlie, Elaine,
Christina, Thomas, Gregory, Brother Quinn,
Miriam, Mark, Angela, Edgar, Annette,
and William, and Marie, and Cecile,
Ophelia, Tessie, Emmy, Annie, Regina,
Daryl, Colby, James, Derek, Johnny, Morvell.
Oh my goodness, there's so many of you
guys.
Robert, Delora, Clara, Shelly,
Abraham, Jeff, Hamilton, and so many more.
Brother Gregory says, I want to welcome
him now.
Brother, I want him now too.
And that's why we have to seek the truth,
right?
Yeah.
Edgar says, now.
Edgar says, I want him now too.
Brothers and sisters, me too.
And that's why the fellowship is so
important.
Okay?
Because you want him now, Gregory?
You want him now, Edgar?
Come on Monday.
Come on Monday's topic.
Alright?
Come on Monday's topic and see what that
is all about.
Alright?
Step by step.
Okay, Gregory and Edgar?
I don't want to spoil the good news just
yet.
But first, let's learn how the prophecies
are fulfilled.
Okay?
Amen.
So yes, the correct answer is B.
When the Lord becomes flesh a second time.
Alright?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Because as you can see, if you wait for
the Lord, brothers and sisters,
if you wait for the Lord to descend on a
white cloud after the disasters,
you're a foolish virgin.
You'll miss God's salvation
and you'll end up weeping
and gnashing your teeth
in the midst of the disasters.
That's no good.
That's no good at all.
Okay?
So take a look here.
In summary, 2,000 years ago, right?
God became flesh.
It was only to forgive our sins.
Right?
It was only to forgive our sins,
brothers and sisters.
But even though our
sins are forgiven, we all
agree that we are
still sinning every day.
So the second coming is divided into two
steps.
Two ways.
One, becoming flesh again, making a group
of overcomers, and after, coming on a
cloud and rewarding the good and punishing
the wicked.
You see?
That's when you know it is over.
When the Lord finally appears on a white
cloud.
Amen.
Brothers and sisters, everyone clear so
far?
Good sharing, everybody.
I know maybe Tessie was not here in the
beginning.
That's okay.
I'll send a review video later on,
okay?
Amen.
Everyone clear so far, brothers and
sisters?
Alright.
Amen, amen.
Anyone else clear?
Devorah, you clear?
Lisa, you clear?
Abraham, are you clear?
Oh, sorry, Shelly.
No worries.
Abraham, clear?
Oh, amen, Colby.
Thanks be to God.
Thanks be to God, Colby.
Annette, clear?
Edgar, clear?
Tessie?
Gregory's clear.
Amen, amen.
Thomas, you clear?
Charlie, clear.
Okay.
So then let us continue, right?
Because we're learning that the Lord is
going to become flesh again.
Now the big question that everyone has is
why?
Why?
Because I know you may be thinking,
well, the Lord already appeared and worked
as the Son of Man 2,000 years ago.
I know you're thinking, why does He have
to become flesh again?
Why does He have to appear as the Son of
Man again?
Some people are literally thinking,
isn't that totally unnecessary?
Couldn't God's Spirit just do the work?
Honestly, brothers and
sisters, what you're thinking or
what you may be thinking
is exactly how I used to think.
I did too.
But I came to an understanding that
whether God works as a Spirit or whether
He works by becoming flesh, it's not for
any of us to decide.
God Himself decides that.
Not me or you.
Come on.
Who's the creator?
Who's the created being?
We are the created being, right?
You see, the method that
God chooses is always based on
the needs of His work and
the needs of corrupt humanity.
You see, God will use
whatever method is best for
His work and most
beneficial for also saving us.
You see, the work God is doing in the last
days is the work of ending the age.
He has a lot of work to do, by the way.
It's not like what people
imagine where He just
shows up in the sky
for a minute and that's it.
No.
First, we've got to be
clear on exactly what
work God is coming
to do in the last days.
Okay, brothers and sisters, we've got to
be clear.
So, let's do some reading.
Let's do some reading, brothers and
sisters.
What is the main reason God needs to
become flesh again?
Well, reason number one.
How many reasons do I have to share here
with you tonight?
Two reasons.
But we'll start with number one first,
okay?
Reason number one.
When God becomes flesh, it's to express
the truth.
It's easier for us to interact with Him
and to truly understand His intentions.
Because, brothers and sisters, we
still do not understand God's intention.
Okay?
We don't.
So, what did the Lord Jesus prophesy?
The Lord Jesus said, now pay close
attention.
He said, I have yet many things to say to
you, but you cannot bear them now.
However, when He, the Spirit of truth has
come, He will guide you into all truth.
John 16, 12-13.
For the Father judges no man, but has
committed all judgment to the Son.
John 5, 22.
And has given Him authority to execute
judgment also, because He is the Son of Man.
John 5, 27.
And if any man hears My words and believes
not, I judge him not.
For I came not to judge the world,
but to save the world.
He that rejects Me and accepts not My
words, has one that judges him.
The word that I have spoken, the same
shall judge him in the last day.
John 12, 47-48.
Now, pay close attention, brothers and
sisters.
Look what the Lord said.
I have yet many things to say to you.
When the Lord is telling you, I have yet
many things to say to you, it means He is
not done speaking and He is not done
working.
You could see 2,000 years ago, the Lord
Jesus had many things He wanted to tell us.
But the people back then couldn't handle
them.
And that is why He saved those words for
the last days.
The Scriptures also mention that the Lord
will use His words to judge people.
This means that when the Lord returns,
He will express the truth and do a stage
of judgment work to purify and save a group
of people, making them into overcomers.
Now, this is where it gets interesting,
okay, brothers and sisters?
Let me ask you something.
I want to see who is paying attention.
Does anyone know who does the work of
judgment in the last days?
Is it the Father or is it the Son?
Who does the work of judgment?
Hmm...
Did anyone catch it?
Which one is it?
The Father or the Son?
I'll wait for just a little bit more.
Amen, amen.
So far, so far, brothers and sisters all
got it right.
So far, everyone got it right so far.
What do you think, Brother Gregory?
Hmm...
All right.
Let's see what the Lord said, brothers and
sisters.
Oh, Brother Gregory, you changing it?
Okay, there you go, Brother Gregory.
Brothers and sisters, good job.
Good job, everyone.
It's the Son.
You're absolutely correct.
Jesus said, for the Father judges no man,
but has committed all judgment to the Son,
and has given him authority to execute
judgment also, because he is the Son of Man.
There's a lot of key words here.
The Father gave authority to the Son to
execute judgment also.
Also, there's a huge point here, also,
brothers and sisters, and I'll tell you soon.
So who's the Father?
Who's the Son?
The Father is the Spirit of God.
The Son is God's Spirit becoming flesh.
Just like in the Old Testament,
God did his work as the Father.
He was the Spirit.
He did his work of issuing the laws and
commandments.
But by the New Testament, the Son came.
God became flesh.
To die on the cross for us.
So 2,000 years ago, the redemption was
done through the Son.
Right?
God became flesh to personally die on the
cross for our sins.
But now, in the last days, the judgment is
also.
What is also?
In addition to.
That's where the Lord said, and has given
him authority to execute judgment also.
Meaning he did the redemption,
but he also does the judgment.
Do you get it, brothers and sisters?
Not only did he do the redemption,
but he also gets to do the judgment.
That's why he will become flesh again.
Because he also has to do the judgment.
Because the judgment is also done by the
Son.
Mystery, eh?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So, now let's continue.
Okay?
So we can understand even more.
So brothers and sisters, think about it.
Right?
If the Lord is returning to express the
truth and to do the work of judgment,
which way is easier for people to approach
and understand him?
God becoming flesh as the Son of Man or
appearing as a spirit?
Which one is easier and more approachable
for us?
A.
God becomes flesh as the Son of Man to
speak to people?
Having human appearance and speaking a
human language?
Or would you say B is easier?
If he just directly spoke to us?
From the sky as a spirit?
Or you don't know these spiritual things?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Which one is easier and more approachable?
Think who we are as a person and what
would be more approachable for God?
That's right, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Felicidad.
That's right, Brother Gregory.
Very, very close, Sister Regina.
Very close, my dear sister.
Amen, Brother James.
But A is actually the answer, Sister
Regina.
And I'll tell you why very soon,
okay, my beloved sister?
But I understand where you're coming from,
Sister Regina.
But actually, A is the best, the best
answer.
And most of you said the Son of Man
appearing would be much easier and
approachable and better to express the
truth.
But I can see why Sister Regina
also might have think, well,
God's spirit can also express
the truth and speak to people.
Why would he have to become flesh?
Well, brothers and sisters, think about
it.
If God's spirit spoke directly to us,
it would not be easy.
Humans would not be able to take it.
And there is a perfect example in the Old
Testament when God did his work directly
as a spirit.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
It's mentioned in Exodus chapter 20,
verses 18 to 19.
It says, And all the people saw the
thunder and the lightning and the noise of
the trumpet and the mountain smoking.
And when the people saw it, they removed
and stood afar off.
And they said to Moses, Speak ye with us,
and we will hear.
But let not God speak with us,
lest we die.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
It's not easy for people to get close to
the spirit.
It's not.
Just this passage alone, you could see
back in the age of law, when God appeared
and spoke to people as a spirit, there
was thunder roaring from the sky, right?
And brothers and sisters, what were their
reactions?
Be honest.
Did they have a happy reaction or were
they scared?
What type of reaction did they have?
Happy or scared when they seen the spirit
of God roaring from the sky?
Exactly.
They were scared.
They were terrified, brothers and sisters.
They were absolutely terrified.
They were so terrified.
What did they say to Moses?
They told Moses, Speak ye with us,
and we will hear.
But let not God speak with us,
unless we die.
They said, don't let God speak to us.
We are going to die.
You go.
You go speak to God, Moses.
You be that medium person between God and
us.
You see, brothers and sisters,
because if God appeared to people as a
spirit, the spirit of God just booms like
thunder from heaven.
You know, imagine a rainy day with
thunder.
That's exactly how God was speaking to
them.
Imagine a rainy day with so much thunder.
Oh, yeah, best believe
they were scared because I
know even when it's
thundering outside, I'm shaking.
I'm scared.
I don't want to be outside.
I want to close all the windows.
I want to start listening
to music so I don't
have to listen to
that thundering voice.
It's frightening.
Right?
How could we not be scared?
How could we get close to the Spirit of
God?
People were terrified.
They didn't want to approach God at all.
Right?
And if that's the case, then he wouldn't
be able to truly reach us.
Right?
If people cannot get close to God,
how could God express the truth?
How could he provide for us?
How could he lead us?
You see, brothers and sisters,
it's only when he becomes flesh.
There you go, my sister, Regina.
Thanks be to God.
Right?
You see, God becoming flesh as the Son of
Man makes it easier to get close to people.
Easier to get close to people.
To lead people to understand God's words
and his will so that they can be saved.
You see, that's why in the Old Testament,
he did as a spirit.
But look in the New Testament.
Look at the picture right here.
That's the New Testament now.
That's God becoming flesh.
Approachable.
Much easier for people to actually get
close to him.
People admired him.
Right?
Because why?
He could use human language to express the
truth.
Because when God
speaks directly as a spirit,
brothers and sisters,
that's not human language.
That's a language that we do not
understand.
It's nothing but wrath.
Right?
It's like when God spoke through Moses
through a burning bush.
Right?
A whirlwind.
They were terrified still.
They had to step all the
way back to understand
what God was trying
to relate to them.
It was not something that people could
actually relate to.
And that's what allows us to better understand
his intentions when he becomes flesh.
Just thinking about Jesus when he was
working.
He could actually be with people.
Talk to them.
Sometimes he used everyday examples like,
you know, to tell parables, like the
parable of the fishing net, or the parable
of the leaven.
And those who love the truth could
actually understand it more, more clearly.
And those were simple stories.
So this shows us that God
becoming flesh as a son
of man makes it easier
to get close to people.
It's far better to lead people to
understand God's words and his words.
His will so that they can be saved.
So let us listen to two spiritual passages
together.
Okay.
Let's listen to two, two spiritual
passages together.
It'll help you better understand why God
becomes flesh and does not do his work
directly as a spirit.
Okay.
I also have an audio for us to listen to.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
Here we go.
God's saving of man is
not done directly using the
method of the spirit and
the identity of the spirit.
For his spirit can neither be touched nor
seen by man.
Neither can man draw near.
If he tried to save man directly using the
perspective of the spirit, man would be
unable to receive his spirit.
salvation.
If God did not put on the
outward form of a created man,
there would be no way for
man to receive this salvation.
For man has no way of
approaching him, much as
no one was able to go
near the cloud of Jehovah.
Only by becoming a created human being,
that is, only by putting his word into the
body of flesh that he is
about to become, can he
personally work the word
into all who follow him.
Only then can man personally see and hear
his word.
And moreover, enter into possession of his
word.
And by this means, come to be full of his
And one more.
One more, brothers and
sisters, to help us understand,
what is the advantage
of God becoming flesh?
Okay?
Here we go.
This was the advantage of God becoming
flesh.
He could take advantage of mankind's
knowledge and use human language to speak
to people and to express his will.
He explained, or translated to man,
his profound, divine language that people
struggled to understand in human language,
in a human way.
This helped people understand his will and
know what he wanted to do.
He could also have conversations with
people from the human perspective,
using human language, and communicate with
people in a way they understood.
He could even speak and work using human
language and knowledge so that people
could feel God's kindness and closeness,
so that they could see his heart.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
You see, I really love these passages
because it explains it.
It's incredibly meaningful
for God to appear
and work by becoming
flesh as the son of man.
And God does this entirely based on the
needs of corrupt humanity.
There is a mystery in all of this that
people often struggle to understand.
You see, in the age of law, God's spirit
appeared and spoke to people.
But those messages were simple.
It was brief, given only occasionally.
But what did the Lord Jesus say?
I have yet many things to say to you.
Meaning, I've got much more to tell you
guys.
Didn't he say that?
This verse tells us that he has many
things to say.
He will guide us into all truth in the
last days.
This means that we will be able to say the
truth in the last days.
This means that to do
the work of judgment in
the last days, God has
to express the truth.
God has to speak a whole lot of words to
actually save people.
And that's why the
spirit speaking directly
is not suitable for the
work of the last days.
Amen, Sister Kim.
That was good, right, Sister?
It's only by becoming flesh
as the son of man can he live
among people, make him
approachable and easy to reach.
And this is so much more effective.
For people to understand the truth.
And at the same time,
this ordinary also exposes
people's notions, imaginations,
and corrupt dispositions.
This way, God can
express the truth that
targets the very essence
of people's corruption.
You know, God can solve our problems,
the problems of our corruption.
He can also rescue us from Satan's power.
So really, brothers and sisters,
you got to think about it.
God becoming flesh a second time in the
last days is one of the greatest blessings
for us who are living in these times.
Amen.
That's the first reason.
Brothers and sisters.
Are we clear so far?
Brothers and Sisters, please mute your
mics.
Okay, please mute your mics.
Everyone clear on the first reason?
Brothers and sisters.
We're clear on the first reason.
Right?
Now, let's take a look at the side.
The second reason, because
there are many sides to the
significance of God becoming
flesh a second time in the last days.
You see, when God returns, he's here to do
the work of judgment, which means using
his words to purify, to save and perfect
people.
But at the same time, his work is meant to
reveal and eliminate people, to sort
everyone according to their kind,
separating the sheep from the goats,
the weeds from the tares, the good
servants from the evil ones, ultimately
rewarding the good and punishing the
wicked.
Now, let's think.
Let's think, okay, brothers and sisters?
Which way is easier
to reveal people's true
colors and their real
attitude toward God?
God appearing as a spirit or God appearing
in the flesh?
Which way is easier?
Which way is easier to reveal people's
true colors?
God appearing as a spirit or God appearing
in the flesh?
Or you're not sure.
Which way do you think would be easier?
And I'll tell you, whatever the answer is,
I'll tell you why, okay?
Amen, Sister Felicidad.
Amen, Gregory.
Amen, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Sister Regina.
Amen, Teresa and Linda.
Amen.
Anyone else, brothers and sisters?
What about Thomas?
Amen, Sister Kim.
Amen.
Exactly, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Brother.
You got it.
Yes, amen.
What about Kenneth?
Deborah?
Bear?
Lisa?
Amen.
Emmy, brothers and sisters, you guys are
on a roll right now.
Y'all are really on a roll.
The Holy Spirit is definitely working in
this room right now.
That's right, Brother Colby.
Amen.
Good sharing, everybody.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
God becoming flesh.
Because you have to think about it.
Right?
If God appeared as a spirit, everyone,
regardless of whether they are good or
evil, would simply just fall down to the
ground and worship him.
And how could he do the work of separating
the good and the evil?
So that's why God coming to work in the
flesh reveals who truly people are.
Let me send you two pictures here.
All right?
Because God, Jesus in the flesh is
ordinary.
You need to hear his voice.
You have to, brothers and sisters.
And then think about it.
Jesus on the cloud.
Right?
Jesus on the cloud is visible to all.
There's no need to hear his voice.
You just have to pay attention by looking
up in the sky.
It means you have no faith at all.
Because looking up in the sky requires no
faith.
But hearing his voice, oh, that's the
ultimate faith.
Because why?
Faith comes from hearing.
Right?
So those who seek
the truth and listen for
the voice of God, those
are the wise virgins.
And even though God in the flesh looks
ordinary and normal on the outside,
the wise virgins can recognize him as the
return of the Lord Jesus.
This perfectly fulfills what the Lord
Jesus told us.
My sheep hear my voice.
I know them.
They follow me.
Foolish virgins, on the other hand,
they see.
They see that God looks normal and
ordinary.
And because of this, they casually judge,
condemn, and resist him.
They're the ones who will be revealed.
They're the ones that will be eliminated
by God.
So God becoming flesh a second time,
it really does show God's wisdom.
It shows how people will be sorted
according to their kind.
The wise virgins from the foolish ones.
The weeds from the tares.
The sheep from the goats.
You see, brothers and
sisters, everyone will be
revealed for who they really
are when God becomes flesh.
Amen.
Alright, brothers and sisters.
You see, after reading the Lord's
prophecy, I'm sure you've all got a better
understanding of how the Lord is coming
back in the last days.
And what kind of work he's bringing.
So let's do a recap.
Okay?
By the way, our fellowship is usually an
hour and a half to an hour and 45 minutes.
Okay?
So let's do a recap
here tonight, brothers
and sisters, of what
we have learned so far.
So, the Lord's return happens in two
stages.
Arriving in secret and arriving publicly.
Before the disasters, he
comes as the Son of Man to
express the truth and to
do the work of judgment.
After the disasters, he
descends on a white cloud in the
spiritual body to reward the
good and punish the wicked.
Alright?
After the disasters, that's when God
becomes flesh a second time and arrives in
secret to express the truth and to do the
work of judgment in the last days.
And what's the main goal?
To make a group of overcomers.
God purifies and saves the sheep who hear
his voice, making them into overcomers,
the firstfruits, and they will enter God's
kingdom.
This entire period is the salvation stage.
Now, after the great disasters, the
Lord descends publicly on a white cloud.
And that's when God will reward the good
and punish the evil.
And all the disbelievers,
all those fake believers,
will be completely
revealed and destroyed.
And only the overcomers
who were made perfect before
the disasters will be
brought into God's kingdom.
So, if you cannot accept the Son of Man
who comes in secret, if you're just
waiting for him to come on a white cloud,
it's going to be too late.
By then, the time of salvation has already
passed.
And the time of punishment has begun.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So now, I've got some questions to ask
you, okay?
We will reveal the answer in the end.
Because I've got three questions to ask.
One, how will God return in the last days?
A.
He'll just come publicly on a cloud
because he already came.
Because he already became flesh 2,000
years ago.
B.
He'll come in secret as a spirit.
Or C.
First, he will become flesh and come in
secret.
And then he will publicly descend on a
white cloud.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
What is the correct answer?
I will just send the answer so you know if
you got it right or if you got it wrong,
okay?
I'll give it five more seconds.
All right, time's up.
Here's the answer.
C is the correct answer.
Great job, everybody.
Now, next question, brothers and sisters.
Next question.
How many times does God become flesh?
A.
Only once.
That was already 2,000 years ago.
Or B.
Twice.
The first time was 2,000 years ago.
And the second time will be in the last
days.
Or C.
Hey, I just got here.
I don't know.
Brothers and sisters.
Five seconds.
All right.
Good job, good job, good job, everybody.
Here is the answer.
B.
Twice.
Good job, everybody.
Now, last question, brothers and sisters.
Last question.
You guys are doing so good, okay?
If you want to be a wise virgin, at
which stage should you welcome the Lord?
A.
When you see the Lord descending on a
cloud as a spirit.
Or B.
When the Lord returns by
becoming flesh a second time
by recognizing and welcoming
him through his words.
Or C.
I'm not sure.
Five seconds.
All right.
Brothers and sisters, good job.
Once again, B is the correct answer.
Thanks be to God.
You see, brothers and sisters?
If we want, by the way, amazing job,
everybody, okay?
I just want to give a clap for everybody.
Yeah, good job.
Good job, everybody.
Good job.
You see, if we want to be a wise virgin,
we really do need to welcome the son of
man who does return in secret before the
disasters hit.
And you know the disasters are about to
hit, brothers and sisters.
And that's exactly why the Lord repeatedly
told us, my sheep hear my voice.
I know them.
They follow me.
Do you know why he said that?
He's telling us that during
his secret arrival, we need to
learn how to listen to the truth
that is expressed by the Lord.
We need to learn the truth so we can
welcome him.
Because the son of man arrives in secret,
he's going to guide us into all truth.
He's going to save us.
And he's going to give us his promises,
brothers and sisters.
All right?
However, however, brothers and sisters,
when he descends publicly on a white
cloud, he's going to come to carry out the
work of judgment.
That's why the Lord tells us to stay awake
and to wait for his secret arrival.
For his secret arrival.
Because if we come to believe just by
hearing this son of man expressing the
truth, before we even see him on a white
cloud, guess what?
We're blessed.
We're really blessed.
We get the chance to be perfected and to
overcome as the first fruits.
And that's an amazing blessing.
It's almost like the days of Noah,
brothers and sisters.
I must bring this up.
The days of Noah, brothers and sisters.
Right?
Because it matters.
It matters whether believers can welcome
the Lord when he returns in the flesh.
Not when he comes back on a white cloud.
There's a huge difference, okay?
Because I'll give you this example.
As the days of Noah were, so shall also
the coming of the son of man be.
Brothers and sisters, we all know the
story of Noah.
We sure do.
You see, God saw the
wickedness on earth and
he decided to cleanse
the earth with a flood.
But before the flood came, he instructed
Noah to warn people and urge them,
get in the ark.
Does it make a difference?
If you enter the ark before the flood or
after the flood?
Absolutely, it makes a difference.
Because those who enter the ark before the
flood, what do they do?
They live.
Those who wait until they see the flood to
enter the ark will be destroyed.
You see, in Noah's time, believing and
listening, that lived.
It led to the salvation.
Because believing comes by hearing.
Faith comes by hearing.
And hearing by the word of God.
That's the salvation period.
That's why the Lord said, my sheep hear my
voice.
You've got to hear to believe,
brothers and sisters.
You've got to believe to hear.
That's the salvation period right there.
But if you're only waiting to see before
believing, you already know.
That will lead you to destruction.
So in the last days, hold that principle.
Because it applies.
It matters whether believers choose to
welcome the Lord's return in the flesh or
if you're just waiting for him to come on
a white cloud.
You see, this choice determines
whether we believers can
receive God's salvation and
enter the kingdom of heaven.
Because what happens
if you're insisting that we
physically see the Lord coming
on a white cloud to believe?
Not only do you lose
your blessing of being
perfected by God,
but you'll be in trouble.
You know who you'll be like, brothers and
sisters?
Thomas.
Yeah, doubting Thomas.
What did the Lord Jesus say to Thomas?
He said, because you have seen me,
you have believed.
He said, the Lord Jesus literally told
Thomas, you believe because you see me.
But what was the second?
Blessed are they that have not seen and
yet have believed.
You get it, brothers and sisters?
The ones that are blessed are not blessed.
They are not the ones that see.
The ones that are blessed are the ones
that believe by hearing.
You see, Thomas was not blessed in the
end.
He waited to see.
And that's why the Lord
says, you're not blessed
because blessed are those
who don't have to see.
Because they can still believe.
Because why?
They have faith.
And where does faith come?
By hearing by the word of God.
So finally, brothers and sisters, let's
listen to the final passage for tonight.
The consequences, okay?
Final spiritual passage for tonight,
okay?
Consequences, brothers
and sisters, of only
waiting for the Lord to
come on a white cloud.
Of only waiting for signs and wonders and
rejecting the truth.
What will happen?
Here we go.
Many people may not care what I say.
But I still want to tell every so-called
saint who follows Jesus that when you see
Jesus descend from the heaven upon a white
cloud with your own eyes, this will be the
public appearance of the Son of
Righteousness.
Perhaps that will be a time of great
excitement for you.
Yet you should know that the time when you
witness Jesus descend from the heaven is
also the time when you go down to hell to
be punished.
It will herald the end of God's management
plan.
And will be when God rewards the good and
punishes the wicked.
For the judgment of God
will have ended before man
sees signs, when there is
only the expression of truth.
Those who accept the truth and do not seek
signs, and thus have been purified,
shall have returned before the throne of
God, and entered the Creator's embrace.
Only those who persist in the belief that
the Jesus who does not ride upon a white
cloud is a false Christ, shall be
subjected to everlasting punishment.
For they only believe in the Jesus who
exhibits signs, but do not acknowledge the
Jesus who proclaims their judgment and
releases the true way of life.
And so it can only be
that Jesus deals with
them when he openly
returns upon a white cloud.
They are too stubborn, too confident in
themselves, too arrogant.
How could such degenerates be rewarded by
Jesus?
The return of Jesus
is a great salvation for
those who are capable
of accepting the truth.
But for those who are unable to accept the
truth, it is a sign of condemnation.
You should choose your
own path, and should not
blaspheme against the Holy
Spirit and reject the truth.
You should not be an ignorant and arrogant
person, but someone who obeys the guidance
of the Holy Spirit and longs for and seeks
the truth.
Only in this way will you benefit.
Amen.
Only in this way can we benefit,
brothers and sisters.
I really hope that everyone loved this
sermon tonight.
And I know some of you may be hesitant,
you may be thinking, we've always been
told that the Lord will return on a white
cloud.
Almost the entire religious world believes
this.
Hey, this may be your
first time that you're
hearing the Lord will
become flesh again.
This idea may be too new for you to
accept.
Well, let me ask you a few questions,
brothers and sisters, right?
Think about it.
Does new automatically mean it's wrong?
Does new mean it's fake?
Did anything we talk about today go
against the Bible?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Just because you're hearing that it's new,
does that mean it's wrong?
Exactly, Felicia.
See that?
What about others?
Does new mean it's fake?
No.
Absolutely no.
Not at all.
You see, because the Bible does clearly
mention there are two ways.
The Lord said it.
I didn't say it.
I'm just sharing what the Lord said.
This perfectly aligns with the prophecies.
We need to... You
know what it is?
A lot of people need to learn to let go of
their own notions and imaginings and stop
blindly defining how the Lord must come
based on one or two verses.
Do you know why the Lord, 2,000 years ago,
right?
Why the Jewish people were
desperately waiting for the Messiah,
and yet when the Messiah
came, they didn't recognize him.
They nailed him to the cross.
You want to know why?
It's because they too used
their imagination to confine
the Messiah with their own
notions and imaginations.
They latched only to a few specific lines
from the prophecies, and they just assumed.
They assumed the Messiah was going to be
born in a palace.
They assumed the Messiah would be like a
king, big and full of muscles.
But hey, the way Jesus came was totally
different from what they had imagined.
You see?
The thing is, they couldn't let go of
their own ideas.
They failed to recognize him.
They nailed him to the
cross, committing a heinous
crime and completely
missing out the Lord's salvation.
Why?
They were stubborn.
They were arrogant, overconfident,
and ignorant.
That's what ruined them.
It's exactly the same situation that we
will face in the last days.
You see, if we stubbornly cling to our old
imaginations or just blindly believe
whatever our pastors tell us,
then we're very likely to make
the same mistake the Jewish
people did, don't you think?
We'll be people who believe
in the Lord but totally miss
his return, losing out on
our salvation in the last days.
You see, God's wisdom is higher than the
heavens.
His work isn't constrained by anyone.
He works according to his own plan and
what we truly need.
Even if the entire human race is against
it or fails to understand it, come on
brothers and sisters, you know that's not
going to change God's plan.
Look at 2,000 years ago.
The entire Jewish nation was against him
when he became flesh.
Did that change God's plan?
It didn't.
God worked on those who can accept him.
So really, God becoming flesh
at second time, brothers and
sisters, and working is a huge
blessing and salvation for us.
For us.
Me and you.
That are listening.
It shows God's love and concern for
humanity.
Because every time God becomes flesh,
it means he faces rejection from the world.
But the ones who actually benefit,
it's always us.
So if you're leaving
this fellowship saying, I
just cannot accept it
because I don't get it.
Well, you're the one that loses out in the
end.
Well instead, why don't you come back?
Come back and continue learning more.
I really hope that everyone treats this
seriously and looks into it.
Because whatever you do, brothers and
sisters, don't miss your salvation.
Don't live with regret for the rest of
your life.
No.
Let's live according to the truth.
Okay?
That's what's important.
Amen, my beloved brothers and sisters.
So with that being said, I've got a review
question.
Okay?
So every time we leave the fellowship,
I do like to ask a review question.
My review question for tonight is, how
does the Lord come back in the last days?
First, in normal flesh or in spirit?
Which one first?
Amen, brother Gregory.
Thank you, brother.
What do you think,
brothers and sisters,
which one will he
become, will he come first?
I almost gave you the answer.
Whoa.
What do you think, Hamilton, Jeff,
Abraham?
By the way, this is just a review
question, okay?
Shelly, Clara, Delora, Bob, Robert,
Lisa, Samuel, Devorah, Johnny,
Derek, James, Colby, Daryl, Regina, Cecile,
Annie, Emmie, Tessie, Ophelia, Marie.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Who else is here?
Quinn, brother Quinn, Mariam, Thomas,
Christina, Gatto, Elaine, Charlie,
Mark, Angela, Edgar.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Amen, amen.
I'm not going to say your answers out
loud.
This is just a review question,
okay?
Because all of you got it right,
so I don't think I need to repeat it.
Good job, everybody.
Good job, brothers and sisters.
So, brothers and
sisters, from tonight's
fellowship, I could see
all of you here tonight.
You've got a heart.
You've got a heart that longs for the
truth.
I'm so happy because I do, too.
I'm hungry for the truth all the time,
brothers and sisters.
And it seems like I met my people,
right?
And maybe each of you have your own way of
getting close to the Lord, but I want to
sincerely say this is not a regular Bible
study.
I think everyone already knows that.
You see, we're here to talk about the
Lord's return.
We're here to prepare to welcome the
And you're going to
hear some truth and
mysteries that you might
have never heard before.
So, over the next few days, we're going to
talk about the mystery of God's judgment,
the mystery of His plan to save humanity.
Also, how to tell the difference between a
true Christ and a false Christ.
And I really hope
that during these days,
you can first focus on
seeking God's kingdom.
Okay?
Focus on seeking God's
kingdom, brothers and
sisters, because that's
what we're doing.
Focusing on seeking God's kingdom.
Alright?
And I really hope that you will not miss
any session.
Tomorrow, at the same
time, we're going to
talk about the mystery
of God's judgment work.
You know that there are over 200 prophecies
in the Bible that talk about judgment?
So this is one of the main work that the
Lord will come back.
Remember, the Bible
says for the time has come
that judgment must
begin at the house of God.
Now ask yourself, who's in the house of
God?
Believers or the non-believers?
It's the believers.
It's us.
And that brings us to a few important
questions.
Why does judgment have to start with us?
If our sins have already
been forgiven, why does
the Lord still need to
do the work of judgment?
Why does judgment have to do with us
entering the kingdom of heaven?
How will the Lord carry out this judgment
work?
How will He judge the believers?
How will He judge the non-believers?
Brothers and sisters, you can see this work
of The judgment is related to me and you.
To every one of us.
It will determine our final outcome.
Where we will ultimately go.
Where we will... and how can we enter the
kingdom of heaven.
So I really hope that you're not going to
miss tomorrow night's topic, okay?
Because you may find a path to entering
the kingdom of heaven.
Thanks be to God.
So brothers and sisters, I just want to
say thank you for joining us.
And after the fellowship, you will see a
smaller group just for you, okay?
Besides this big group
that everyone is in, you'll
see a second group
which is just your group.
It's a group where you can ask me
questions.
Where we can chat one-on-one.
Where you can ask me for prayer requests.
We can get to know one another,
okay?
So after the fellowship is done, I'm
planning a three-minute call with all of you.
To see whether you have any questions.
So I do want to make sure that it fits
into your schedule.
So can everyone tell me which time works
best for you?
So I can call you for three minutes.
You can do A, after the sermon is good.
I can call you when we're done here.
Or do you prefer tomorrow at 8 a.m.
to 7-8 a.m.?
You can choose which one fits best for
your schedule, okay brothers and sisters?
I'm leaving it right there for you.
I do want to respect your schedule.
So, you can pick whatever time works best
for you.
And I'll give it a call.
But if you don't pick a time, then I guess
I'm calling everybody tonight.
Since it's Friday night, we're not doing
anything.
We're here.
We're together.
Might as well just talk, right?
So, I can do that.
If you don't give me a time, I'll call you
after the sermon.
That's no problem.
It'll only take three minutes.
I really just want to say hello.
I want to fully formally introduce myself
and you can do the same.
And I invite you to come back again,
okay?
Amen.
I got you, Colby and Regina.
I'll definitely call you after the sermon.
All right, Edgar.
I'll call you from six to seven.
Teresa, I see you.
Six to seven.
Sister Rachel, two to four.
Perfect.
Perfect, brothers and sisters.
Gregory, after the sermon, you got it.
My brother, Emmy, from 12 to two.
Got you.
I'll reserve all my time for you guys.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to... thanks be to Almighty God.
All right.
With that being said, let's do a quick
prayer together, okay?
I do encourage you to come back tomorrow
because we're going to...
we're going to talk about a topic that
relates to our entry into the kingdom.
So let's do a prayer together,
okay?
Let's pray.
Amen.
Dear Heavenly Father,
Almighty God, we thank
you for an incredible
time together, dear God.
We really did feel the Holy Spirit working
in each and every single one of us.
We're very thankful, dear God,
to be a part of this community that really
seeks the truth wholeheartedly,
dear God.
We're seeking the truth for you.
We're seeking the truth for you,
dear Lord.
We're seeking the truth in order to
welcome you.
And this is something that
we all love and that we all
adore, dear God, because we
all have a heart that loves you.
We just want to prepare ourselves.
We do want to be a wise virgin in the last
days, dear God.
We don't want to be a foolish virgin that
rejects you.
So here we are, dear God.
Here we are preparing,
preparing the oil in
order to be fully equipped
for when you return.
And dear God, as we depart from the
fellowship, I really wish to get to know
each and every single brother and sister
here.
I really feel we're already so close
within your words, dear God.
And I also pray for them.
I know that outside of the fellowship,
they have their own lives.
They have their own difficulties,
dear God, whether it's a health problem,
financial problem, whatever it is,
dear God, I pray that you be with them,
that you lead them in the right direction.
That you guide them in their day-to-day
life.
We can't do life without you, dear God,
for you are the one that gave us life.
You are the one that breathed your life
into us.
We're here because of you.
So I pray that whatever we do in life,
dear God, makes you happy, resonates with
your truth, and is able to carry out your
will.
So dear God, we thank you once again for
this time of fellowship.
And I pray that we can continue to come
back tomorrow and to learn more,
to equip ourselves with the truth,
to grow more within your truth.
Your words, dear God.
If you gave me a time for tomorrow,
yes, I'll give you a call tomorrow.
Okay, brothers and sisters, you're more
than welcome to open up your mic.
And you can say goodnight to each other.
Okay.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Yeah, you can open up your mic if you if
you know how to.
If not, it's okay.
We'll practice tomorrow.
Praise be to God.
Good night, everybody.
Good night, Colby.
Good night, Emi.
Good night, Regina.
Good night, Miriam and Gregory.
Good night, Edgar and Smiley and Felicidad
and Linda, Gloria, Teresa.
Good night, Abraham and Thomas.
I'll talk to you guys very soon.
Okay.
Goodbye for now.